Hey, Raj, can you tell me about machine learning?
I've been wondering, yaar. What's the big deal about it,
yaar? Machine learning is actually quite interesting.
See, basically, it's a type of artificial intelligence that
helps systems learn from data, right? You know, like how we learn
from our experiences. ML algorithms learn from the data they're
trained on. Oh, really? But how does it work exactly?
Tell me now, is it like super complicated or something?
No, yaar, it's not that complicated, actually.
You know, ML algorithms can be broadly classified into supervised,
unsupervised, and reinforcement learning. See,
supervised learning is like learning from labeled data.
Unsupervised is like finding patterns in unlabeled data.
And reinforcement learning is like learning from trial and error.
Right. It's used in many applications like image recognition,
natural language processing, and more.